Rotator cuff repairs, I
think 17 million people
from a rotator cuff.
Probably anyone, if you sat
next to you in any sort of
retirement home community,
any
sort of thing over 60
living, one out of three
are going to have a rotator
cuff pathology.
And so what we know is that
they occur.
We're really good at fixing
them.
We're not great at getting
them to heal.
And I tell people in Palm
Beach, 90 is the new 70.
And the reality is, guess
what?
Our blood cells, our biology
isn't as good as when we
were 20.
So if you can create some
sort of scaffold to make
better, to give you a better
chance to be 20 again, or
40, or maybe even just 60
again, you're going to get
better
healing of that rotator
cuff.